Mojtaba Namazi Fard

Front-End Developer

DoB: 1998-08-03

Military Service: Served

anf.namazi@gmail.com

(+98)9210886520

09900890108

anfnamazi.github.io/Resume

Tehran, Iran

Profile Summary

I have 4+ years of experience in React development and work with 3 software companies in the team, I enjoy staying up-to-date with the latest web development trends and technologies. Seeking a challenging role to contribute technical expertise, creativity, and problem-solving skills to a dynamic development team.

Work Experience

Front-End Developer

Sharif hamrah pazhoohan

Tehran, Iran

March 2019 - Present

Tasks and Achievements

- Participated in the planning and execution of sprints, ensuring timely delivery of high-quality code.
- Implemented performance optimization strategies for adding large amounts of data to the map container.
- Conducted code reviews to maintain code quality and adherence to coding standards.

Front-End Developer

Dade kavan | Andishe bartar

Tehran, Iran

September 2021 - December 2021

Tasks and Achievements

Successfully led the redesign of food ordering process resulting in a 40% increase in user engagement.

Front-End Developer

Himart

Tehran, Iran

December 2020 - December 2021

Tasks and Achievements

Implemented strategies for filtering and sorting shops in near area.

Skills

Git / Git flow Agile / Scrum Javascript / Typescript React.js HTML / CSS / SASS

Redux / Mobx / Context-api Graph-QL / Rest-API Leaflet.js / Cesium.js Bootstrap / Material ui

Education

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Branch: Software

Institute/University: Sadra

Tehran, Iran 2016 - 2020

Language

English: Intermediate

Certificates

React

Institute: Sharif University Free Education

October 2019

Social Network





